My name is David Andre and here is how
to build AI agents with Nano Banana.
Now, what even is Nano Banana? It's a
new AI model from Google that is by far
the best image model in the world. It's
the first AI model in history to be
great at editing images with great
consistency. I mean, look at these
examples. The consistency and
reliability is just incredible. Now,
while most people focus on the model
itself, which is fine, nobody really
talks about what you can build with it.
So the real opportunity with Nanobanana
is actually building multi- aent systems
where each of the AI agents is powered
by Nano Banana and this is possible
because it's actually a version of
Gemini. So it can not only output text,
it can also make decisions and most
importantly take agentic actions. So in
this video I'll show you step by step
how to build a team of AI agents powered
by Nano Banana. And you can do this even
if you are a complete beginner. First
off let me show you just a few of the
use cases that this incredible model can
do. new clothing design, thumbnail
concepts for social media, product shots
for e-commerce, drop shipping, logos,
banners for any type of business,
restoring photos such as old photos in
low quality or black and white photos.
So, not only can it create images, which
is already pretty good, but it can edit
them with insane consistency. I mean,
look at this. I asked to make the cloud
a bit bigger and everything else the
same except for the cloud getting a bit
bigger. This is the first AI model in
history that can do this. So, if you
want to use nano banana for free, just
go to vectal.ai. So now that you
understand just how powerful Nano Banana
is, let's use it to build some AI
agents. All right. So inside of cursor,
let me open an empty folder right here.
Boom. And actually I'm going to use clot
code for this. So open a terminal and
just type in cloth. If you don't have
installed cloth code, what are you
doing? It's one of the best tools for
coding. And I have about a dozen videos
on it. So just watch any of them after
this video, of course. Now let me
actually show you what we will be
building because this is incredible. So
we will create a system where you can
generate multiple images and then create
variations of them using multiplayer
agents all powered with nano banana.
That way you don't have to just do one
image. You can do four variations, six
variations and then branch out from them
in this nice tree UI. And I'll even show
you how you can use the nano banana API
for free. So the first thing I'm going
to do is create a new file. So let me
just right click, click on new file. And
this is going to be the project details.
And here I'm going to describe what the
project is about at a high level. Now
feel free to pause and read this prompt,
but it's basically what I described,
just a way to interact with Nano Banana,
but in a multi- aent system, and you can
use this to build any application
because this is the real opportunity.
The image editing capabilities of this
model just unlocked hundreds of new
possible startup ideas. So if you are
serious about AI and you want to start
building AI agents, make sure to watch
until the end. All right, let me jump
into cloud code and I'm going to switch
into auto accept mode. By the way, for
the model, I'm using Opus because it's
the best model. Now, the first thing I'm
going to say is read project details.
That way, it's up to date with what
we're building. Your first task is to
Boom. And this is my first prompt.
Again, feel free to pause and read it.
The full name of this model, the public
name is Google Gemini 2.5 Flash image
preview. Now, no wonder this name didn't
stick. People remember it as Nano
Banana, which is the internal name
Google gave this model. So, this is
actually the official name of this
model, and you can use it either through
the Google AI studio or just on open
router. So this is basically what the
first prompt is about connecting this
exact string with the ability to save
the resulting image locally. Now of
course we're going to build on top of
this so that at the end we have a nice
UI with multiple AI agents running all
powered by Nano Banana. Now a common
mistake that a lot of people make when
they get into coding with AI is not
providing examples and they get shitty
results because of the prompt being so
bad. Instead you want to clearly
describe what you're building and you
want to give it examples. So what I'm
going to do is I'm going to use XML tags
to paste in the official docs. Right? So
on open router you can click on API and
they literally tell you what code you
should have to run this model. All you
need to do is click on copy and paste it
into cloud code as an example. And the
reason I wrap it in XML tags is just for
the model to have better context
engineering. So it's a nice little
prompt engineering tick. And then when
using cloud models always make sure to
say think hard answer in short. This
actually isn't only a prompt engineering
tactic. This directly impacts the
reasoning effort of the model. If you
say think hard, clawed models such as
Opus or Sonet will dedicate more
reasoning effort and give you much
better outputs than if you don't say it.
Now, while this is running, we still
have to create the ENV file ourselves.
So, just right click in your project and
type in ENV. And actually, um, Cloud
Code gave us an example of what it
should look like. So, we can just copy
this. Let's go back into open router.
Click on top right. Click on credits. If
we look at the cost, it's very cheap. It
costs like three cents for a single
output. Right there it is. 0.03 03
dollar for an output image which means
you can create like 30 images per
dollar. So for $3 you can create nearly
100 different images with NO Banana
which is pretty incredible. Now as I
promised let me show you how to use this
model for free inside of open hour they
have this free version and this one as
you might expect costs zero. Now the
caveat is that obviously it has some
rate limits and the uptime is going to
be worse than the paid ones. You can see
there's some major drops where only 30%
of the requests were getting through.
Either way, we need an API key. So,
click on the top right, click on keys,
click on create API key. I'm going to
name it subscribe. If you're watching
this, make sure to subscribe. It takes
two seconds. It's completely free, just
like that, a banana, and it helps out a
lot. So, go below the video and click
subscribe. Okay? I'm going to create a
key. Copy. Do not share API keys with
anybody. Treat them as passwords. I'm
going to delete my key before uploading
this video, okay? So, don't try to steal
it or you can try. It's up to you. But
just paste it after this like so. And
click save. We can close the environment
file. Now, close code should be
finished. And there we go. So it's
finished with the first prompt.
Beautiful. So to use this, all we need
to do is add the API key, which we just
did. And then run pip install require
txt. So let's do that right now. Boom.
Just paste it in. We don't have pip.
Okay. So I'm going to show you how to
solve with AI if you've never
encountered this issue. But I can just
uh copy this. Boom. Help me solve this
error. Think harder in short. So
obviously I've encountered this issue in
the past but if you haven't you can use
AI agents to solve any error you might
encounter right so uh commandfound pip
okay python 3 I'm install okay so I'm
going to actually I'm going to ask it
help me set up a new cond env for this
and solve the issue there is great for
managing Python environments create now
a banana python 3 I'm going to allow
that boom and then all we have to do is
do activate and the project name boom
and there we go So next, let's try
installing the dependencies again. Okay,
so now it's installing all the required
packages for this project and I can type
clear and let's see if we can just run
this. So I'm going to click on the
Python file here. So do we have these
installed? Okay, actually one thing I
need to do is below my webcam right
here, you can see the Python version. I
need to enable it inside of cursor. So
let me do nano banana. Boom. This is the
new condenv. And now these errors should
disappear. There we go. Let's run this.
Okay, so sending prompt generated
description of beautiful sunset and
here's the response and it created a new
image. So let's click on folder outputs
and why is it a text file? Okay, so this
is obviously a mistake. So I'm going to
describe it. The result should be a PNG
file, not a text file. Let me paste in
the model name again. Boom. Here's the
model name. This is the exact model name
on open router. It can output images.
So, make sure we save the image, not the
text response. Think hard answer in
short. So, it's actually good that I
didn't do it on the first try because I
can show you the real authentic
experience of what it's like to building
stuff with AI because you will run into
errors. The key is not taking those
errors personally, clearly describing
them, and using the AI agents to fix
them. All right, so it made some changes
to support B 64. Okay, looks good. It
actually saved a bunch of lines as well.
So, let's run again. should be
completed. All right, let's run this
script again. And it's running. Let's
see if we save a PNG image as a result.
Fail to generate image. Okay, now
another way to fix errors faster is to
do web search. So you can use Perplexity
for this if you have Plexi Pro. In the
meantime, let's see if Cloud Code
managed to fix it. So let's rerun the
script. Boom. Again, generated image of
a beautiful sunset over mountains. And
we expect the PNG to be saved. And there
it is. We have the exact beautiful
sunset over mountains image. And this is
the first step in building our multi-
aent system. Again, we're going to build
on top of this. But now we know that our
code works. Our code is solid. And we
can generate an image based on a pro,
which is the foundation. When building
something with AI, you don't want to
oneshot a big project. You want to split
it into five, 7, 10 smaller stages, and
then execute each stage individually,
building on top of the last one. That
way, if you encounter any errors, just
like we did here, you can fix them
before adding more complexity into your
codebase. So, I'm going to say, great
work. Now it's time to add multi-image
support. Boom. Here's my prompt. TLDDR.
Instead of one, open router API call, do
four different calls, each one resulting
in a separate PNG file. And I'm also
going to say the fewer lines of code
changed the better. This is another
great way to reduce unnecessary feature
bloat complexity in your codebase. A lot
of the times the AI models have a
tendency to write more lines of code
than necessary, right? But if you say
the fewer lines of code the better, you
will get a simpler, cleaner version that
a lot of times works just as well, if
not better than the more bloated code.
All right, so let's see what's
happening. It's creating a simple Flask
app which is a lightweight Python UI
framework. So our codebase is super
simple. Look at this. Like we literally
have two code files and environment
file. That's kind of incredible to be
honest where you can build in a very
simple codebase. You don't have to bloat
your stuff with unnecessary packages and
dependencies. You can just use raw
Python which is one of the most popular
languages in the world. And the beauty
of that is the models are actually
trained on it because there's a lot of
training data in Python. So the app is
ready to run. Let's see if Cloud Core
gives us the instructions and it does.
So we need to install Flask. So I'm
going to open the terminal again. I'm
going to do clear. I'm going to do pip
install flask. All right, there we go.
So since we have the cond environment
enabled, it's nicely separated from my
other projects that don't use Flask. And
then we start the app with Python app.
py. So it gives us the URL, which is
just localhost 8000. And we can open
that. It actually opened on my second
screen. Let me drag that over. Boom. So
here is the results. We can nicely see
them. So you don't have to use them in a
terminal, right? It's a nice simple web
user interface, which is nice because
it's easier to use. Then we can test
whether it can generate a new image. So
let's test that. Actually, I'm going to
do a blue dog in a 1930s garden. Just
random prompt. Generate. It says
generating, but I don't know if that's
already wired up. Let's see if stuff is
happening in our back end. Four or four.
That's favicon though. Generating from
variations. Let's see if this works. The
UI is very simple. I mean, we have some
on hover, but it's nothing crazy. Just
loading results. Okay. Generating four
images in parallel. So, it's promising
because it generated the prompt
variations with GPT5 mini and it's
saving the dog examples. We might need
to reload. I don't think we have
automatic refresh in the front end, so
we might just need to reload it. Oh,
there we go. It did reload. And there we
have four very different. Yeah, these
are very, very unique. Wow. Not bad at
all. So, yeah, here we have it. So, we
have the UI. So, we're actually
progressing very, very fast. The next
stage is to add image editing and
uploads. So, I'm going to say great
work. Just compliment AI, you know,
doesn't hurt. The next stage is adding
image editing and image uploads. So,
boom. Here's the prompt. Execute this
in the simplest way possible. Think hard
answer in short. All right. So, while
this is running, let's utilize our
multi-cloud code setup. I'm going to say
we have updated since you have to
realize this cloud code didn't do the
web stuff. So, we need to tell it about
the new web changes. We've updated our
app by adding app. I'm going to tag the
file. Your task is to execute this. And
I'm going to wrap this in XML tags
again. Next step. Boom. Paste it in.
Close that. Slashn next step. Implement
this next step in a clean, simple, and
minimal way. just like a 10x engineer
would think hard answer in short. Okay,
so let's check in. So we're going to
launch this cloud code agent and let's
check in on the first one which seems to
be finished. So let's go back. Let's see
if we can upload images. Let's reload
our front end. And there we go. We can u
we can choose a file. So maybe let's use
something from the presentation such as
this um Gemini logo. I'm going to save
it to documents. So upload selected and
I I can say uh make the selected
image more vibrant and colorful. Okay.
So let's see if it can use this image to
generate a new variation. So far we've
generated only stuff from scratch which
previous models like midjourney or
stable fusion were able to do. However,
this model Nano Banana is excellent at
image editing. So now we're passing it
an image and let's see if it can
generate variations from it. Now, while
that's doing, we should check on our
other cloud code. Now, this is probably
not the not the most um like best
practices stable way of development.
This is definitely more yolo side. If
you want to make progress faster, you're
also going to run into errors and you're
going to you're going to probably be
more confused if you don't know what
you're doing. If you're a beginner,
probably stick to a single instance of
cloud code or a single instance of
codeex. Otherwise, you'll be confused,
right? So, we're we're doing a lot here,
but uh that also could save us some
time. So, let's see what's happening
here. Reloading. Okay, generating. Okay,
we have the chat assistant now. So, that
kind of that kind of messed up our test
because Okay, I'm going to tell it no,
don't start anything. Just execute what
I asked. So, basically, the next stage
was adding the conversational assistant,
but I just wanted to test this image.
make the attached image more colorful
and vibrant.
Right? Generate. There's something very
curious on open router which I want to
talk about. Why is GPT5 mini such a low
throughput? Look at this. 40 tokens per
second. If you look at GPT5, the main
one, not mini, it's literally sometimes
faster. I mean, look at this throughput,
right? Sometimes it's like 50. like how
is what what's going on OpenAI? I don't
understand. GBD5 mini is sketch. But
anyways, let's go back. Let's see if we
have the variations of our image. We
have some variations, but they are not
of our image. That is an issue we have
to address. But before we do that, let
me test the conversational assistant.
So, I'm going to say uh create an image
of a tree growing in the void. Okay. So,
not much seems to be happening here.
Okay. So it did result with some images
but it reset our chat which is not good.
So first let's focus on this. Okay let's
focus on getting the image editing to
work. So let's see what's going on.
Choose image file. So I'm going to say
actually let me speak it into existence.
So right now we actually have a bug
where the attached image isn't being
properly passed to the model. So
whatever prompt I send it's kind of not
relevant to the image I upload. So
analyze that part of your codebase and
think hard about why we're facing this
issue and what is the proper way to fix
it. And actually a lot of people don't
even know that cloth code has built-in
web search. So I could say browse the
web to see the proper way to use open
router API to pass images to multi-
multimodal AI models. Follow the latest
open router docs. Okay. So let's approve
web search because um this is one of the
tools you want cloth code to be running
without asking for permission. Okay, I
don't know why the web search failed.
That's very interesting. Anyways, let's
refresh this.
Okay, so again I asked it to flip it
upside down which it didn't do with the
it creates some upside down images but
like it's not doing it with these
attached ones. So that's a problem. So
what you should do if you're stuck on
something is just do a deep research
right whether it is perplexity whether
it's Chad GBD Gemini doesn't matter just
well it does matter but you know
whatever I think perplexity is a nice
balance of speed and um quality the best
one probably is it's hard to say Gemini
has improved theirs a lot so either
Gemini or OpenAI check GBDB research but
basically I asked it to check the open
router docs to check like 50 plus
sources on how to pass images as parts
of the prompts, right? Because this is
the issue here. Uh, cloud core is
already doing stuff. So, let's see if
those clo fixes work. What I'm going to
do is I'm going to clean the folder
here. Boom. Let's delete that. Let's
refresh. I'm going to say flip the
attached image upside down. Generate.
All right. So, this deep research is
finishing up. That's good. Maybe cloud
code will manage to fix it by itself.
You know, a lot of the times that is the
case. Okay. So, we have some problem. We
don't really want to. Do we want prompt
variations on this? Maybe. We'll see, I
guess. Okay, so let's see what happens.
No, it's still not passing the image.
So, I'm I'm going to describe that
issue. The image that the user attaches
needs to go to the nano banana Gemini
model, which is the one that can
generate new images. Below is the
official documentation from open router
on how to do this correctly. All right.
So, I described the issue in a detailed
way and then I'm going to pass the docs
as well.
Boom. And actually, I'm going to do
something radical, which is resetting a
cloth code, which sometimes you have to
do like when there's too much stuff.
This is called context, by the way. When
there is too much stuff, uh, the
performance can drop. So, what I'm going
to do is create a fresh cloth code. Just
paste in the new context. I'm going to
end it with docs. I'll say implement a
clean and minimal fix
like a senior developer would.
think harder answer in short. So
sometimes literally just switching to a
new cloth code does the trick. You kind
of have to develop a feel for when that
is the correct move. So sometimes you
just have to be willing to get your
hands dirty and do some good old
debugging. So I asked it to add three
debug log statements at the essential
parts where it makes sense. And we're
going to see what's happening to the
image as I send it. And actually, you
know what? Since cloud code isn't
solving this, I'm going to turn on uh
the codex extension and get some more
power behind us. Flip the attached file
upside down. I'm going to copy the logs.
I'm going to say logs.
Logs.
Here is what our backend terminal looks
like. What does this tell us? What and
what is the next step we should take in
debugging this
think hard answer in short
in the meantime what we can do is copy
this deep research as well I'm going to
say uh docs
docs I'm going to say the same issue
just describe it to codeex we are facing
issue where the when the user attaches
an image and he sends a prompt where he
just wants the image to be edited it
doesn't make it to the Gemini model.
Somehow the image is lost along the way
and the model just generates variations
that are completely irrelevant to the
attached image. Do not make any changes
yet. Just answer. Be concise. Page was
reloading after upload wiping selected
image from memory. Oh my god. If that's
the case, that's going to it's kind of
disappointing. Take the attached image
and flip it upside down. Okay, so we
have some debug outputs. So this is
giving me hope. Let's see. Does this
reload? Let me refresh. Oh, there we go.
Finally. And it's actually good. Gemini.
Wow. 2.5 flash. This is very impressive,
guys. Wow. That's crazy. That's actually
kind of crazy to be honest. So, we've
defeated this step. Beautiful.
Uh, it was a dumb issue, but some debug
logs expose the issue. So, that's that.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to do
compact so we can reset the context a
bit. And we're going to focus on making
the conversational
chat work. And actually, I'm going to
interrupt this prompt. I'm going to
switch to low. And we're going to
speedrun the conversational
chat because uh I'm not sure this works.
So, generate an image of a blue dog
battle boarding. Okay, let's see. When
we copy that prompt, let's see if this
actually works or not. And we'll say um
goal boom goal verify whether this has
been implemented fully and properly
answer in short. Okay. So does this work
or not? Reload. What is happening? Right
now this feature doesn't work at all. Uh
the messages get lost. The chat history
is not persisted. We should be saving it
in some JSON or some SQLite database.
But the main issue is that it doesn't
work. So make sure to refactor the chat
conversational functionality, the chat
assistant, not only to have a nicer UI,
but also to actually work. Okay, so I'm
going to do something crazy. I'm going
to start working on the tree
functionality. I'm going to do feature.
I'll say execute this feature like a a
10x engineer would. The UI should be
clean, minimalist, impressive, and
interactive. Built on top the existing
codebase. Do not refactor what works.
Think hard, answer short. So I'm going
to start a codeex with highing effort on
the tree UI which I showed you earlier.
I mean honestly like the you know that's
not needed for the main functionality
but uh I want to show that. So my goal
with this is to literally show you what
I built earlier today in vectal. So I
already solved these issues once. So
it's kind of frustrating for me to do
this again. Uh I guess it's my fault not
remembering the solution. But anyways, I
implemented the exact same thing in
vector, right? So you can just select
the nanobanana model and you can say
generate
an image of a blue dog paddle boarding
on a huge Hudson River in NYC. So I was
just in NYC. The vlog is coming soon.
So, make sure to subscribe not to miss
the David Andre New York City vlog. But
let's see. So, sure. Here you go. And
there we go. This is definitely New
York. So, we have the blue dog. And look
at this. Like Hudson River. Amazing.
Brooklyn Bridge. Crazy. This is crazy
good, actually. I'm going to say add a
cat on the paddle board as well. Keep
everything the same. So, again, the goal
with what I'm showing you here is
literally practicing what I preach,
right? I built this in vector. I'm not
gatekeeping anything. Okay, so this is
annoying bug. I'm going have to fix
that. But it should still generate the
image. There we go. There we go. Look at
this consistency, guys. This has never
been possible until Nano Banana. We have
a dog and we have like this is crazy.
This is insane. This is incredible.
Incredible. So yeah, all of you can use
Nanobanana in vectal for free. But I'm
also showing you how you can build your
AI agents in case you want to build a
SAS, in case you want to build a startup
for a specific niche with this. Just
follow what I'm doing in this video and
I'm also showing you how to debug this.
What is happening here? A Python app.
No, while I did not give you permission
to launch the app, it's already running.
Okay. Okay. Let's test out the
assistant. Let's see if it's fixed. But
I'm not going to stress too much over
that. So, I'm going to say generate an
image of an abstract tree. Send. Let's
check the back end terminal. So look how
long codeex is thinking. It can it can
think for like five seven minutes
easily. Clo doesn't have that much
reasoning. So this is already better. We
haven't lost the message and we see some
UI here.
Let's see if this actually works.
Sometimes it fails. You can see that
nana banana is not that stable. Okay. So
it generated the rows northern abstract
tree. Let's see if that's finished or
not. So the responses aren't being
displayed properly. That's unfortunate.
But we have the codeex making the tree
interactive tree in the meantime. So
that might be fighting with our changes
again trying to do multiple things at
once to save time. Let's start our app
again. We have the start command here.
Super simple. We go. Let's open the
local host
tree.
Okay. So here we have the dashboard.
Let's upload something. This doesn't
really work though. The upload button in
the tree canvas doesn't really work.
Generant enter prompt. Press E to jump
to the chat.
I mean, we there's like a lot of
potential here, but we just don't have
it. Okay. Upload. Oh, there we go. Let's
go. Okay. Oh, let's go. We're cooking
here. Let's click on variant. Is
something happening? So, we have, look
at this. We have an image on the board.
It's much more visual, much more
interactive. can say great job the issue
is fixed. However, when I click variant,
nothing happens. Instead, what should
happen is we should send a simple prompt
to the GBD5 mini agent which is
responsible for generating four
variations and then it should generate
the four variations using the existing
code which works and then we should show
these on the canvas in the tree search.
Analyze the codebase, figure out where
the issue is and make sure that the
variant
button actually works. So really the way
you want to work is use cloth code for
explanation. Cloth code should be
upsklling yourself. It should be gaining
understanding for yourself and
generating new ideas. But most of the
time Codex has better ideas and you can
actually compare these you know give the
output from cloud code into Codex. Give
the output from COX into cloud code.
This is literally how I work every
single day. But uh you want to use both
and CEX is more powerful right now. So
again, if you want me to make a full
video on that, comment below with the
word codeex and also subscribe. If I see
a lot of people subscribing, I'm going
to make that video because it is the
most OP AI agent as of right now. Yeah.
So this is um this is a time to again
debug this a bit. Even though this is
already a huge step in the right
direction, I do want to show you guys
the branching out because that is the
that is the most impressive part to be
honest. So I just wanted to add some u
debug log statement so we can actually
be strategic and not just randomly
not do anything. When I click the
variant button in the tree view nothing
happens. Investigate why that is and
answer in short. Do not make any
changes. Okay. Wait. So we have some
front end. Is it going to be front end
console or back end console? Okay. Yeah.
This is going to be front. Let's see.
Variant.
Am I crazy? What's going on? Okay. This
is very strange. This button doesn't
even work in the console doesn't
display. So might be issue with the
fundamental UI
like the click isn't even registered
here. Okay, cloud code is suggesting
that the click handler is the problem.
So now both of these agents are fighting
against each other because both are
trying to change the same file. Oh,
let's go. Let's go. So, this is very bad
UI, but I'm going to say uh
more
colorful versions. Okay. Okay. Boom.
There we go. All right. We are back on
we're back on track. So, we have the
four versions generating. Nice. This is
nice.
This blue box is kind of annoying.
Remove the blue box um of the tree view.
Network error we're creating. Wait.
Okay. We got a network error. That's not
the best. Okay. Oh, it worked. It
actually worked. Never mind. So, after a
bunch of errors, we got it to work. This
is This is nice. This is nice. And then
we can hover over any of these and make
a variant. So, let's say I like this
one. Boom. Variant. I say u
rotate each version by 90°. I don't
know. Okay. And there we go. Look at
this. And this is the tree UI that is
like much nicer to work with images than
just chat, right? So this is an example
of a single app you can build and even
though I faced a bunch of errors, it
took me like 90 minutes to build this
right in grand total amount of time.
And I'm definitely not a professional
developer. So if you want to take Nano
Banana and turn it into a startup, you
know, maybe you're targeting clothing
companies like some of our new society
members do, maybe you're targeting um
social media, right? like Facebook ads
creatives for marketing campaigns, maybe
you want to make thumbnails for
YouTubers, whatever you want to do. The
opportunities are endless with this
model. Like stuff like this wasn't even
possible a week ago. So, that's why I'm
so hyped about it. That's why I
literally couldn't sleep today. I woke
up at like 3:00 a.m. and I added it into
vectal because um yeah, this is a
revolutionary model for different
reasons, right? It's not like better
than midjourney at generation. It's
better at consistency. Like this is
crazy. Everything else is the same here.
It just added the cat and it looks super
good. Like the cat isn't like glitched
or anything. It's amazing. So, if you
want to try Nano Banana yourself, go to
vectal.ai. Just type it in, create an
account. Super easy. Takes 30 seconds
and you can use it for free. Even on the
free plan, you can use it. If you want
unlimited access, however, Veal Pro
members get unlimited access to Nano
Banana inside of the chat. And let me
know what you think of this full screen
functionality. A lot of you guys have
requested it, so we added it. So now you
can chat with actal just like you can
with chat GBT. So with that being said,
thank you guys for watching. Hopefully
you enjoy this video. If you want me to
make more videos on Nana Banana, comment
below and I wish you a wonderful
productive week. See you.